<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleEffectTextRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <effectTextList>
  
	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_FlowState">
		<Name>Flow State</Name>
		<Desc>Increase minimum and maximum roll value of all dice by +1.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Cycle">
		<Name>Cycle</Name>
		<Desc>Upon using a page, discard 1 random page, then draw 1 page, then lose 1 Cycle.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_InfernalOverheat">
		<Name>Overheat</Name>
		<Desc>{0} Speed dice become unusable. This character's rightmost Speed die cannot become unusable from this effect. Lose 1 Stack at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_SparkSamsara">
		<Name>Samsara</Name>
		<Desc>Used in order to use Speed Break. Can be gained by gaining Haste and by using Combo Finisher Combat Pages.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_SparkSpeedBreak">
		<Name>Speed Break</Name>
		<Desc>Moving faster than visible motion.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Lightning_Orb">
		<Name>Lightning Orb</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of the Scene, deal 3 damage to a random enemy. If this Orb is Evoked, deal 8 damage to a random enemy.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Frost_Orb">
		<Name>Frost Orb</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of the Scene, gain 3 Shield. If this Orb is Evoked, gain 7 Shield.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Darkness_Orb">
		<Name>Darkness Orb</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of the Scene, gain 3 Malice. If this Orb is Evoked, deal 6 damage to the enemy with the lowest HP.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Plasma_Orb">
		<Name>Plasma Orb</Name>
		<Desc>Gain +1 Max Light Capacity. At the start of the Scene, restore 1 Light. If this Orb is Evoked, restore 2 Light at the start of the next Scene.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Focus">
		<Name>Focus</Name>
		<Desc>Lightning Orbs deal +{0} additional damage. Frost Orbs gain +{0} additional Shield. Gain +{0} additional Malice from Darkness Orbs, and deal +{0} additional damage with Darkness Orbs.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Malice">
		<Name>Malice</Name>
		<Desc>When Evoking a Darkness Orb, it deals +{0} additional damage. After Evoking a Darkness Orb, lose all Malice.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_Orb_Lockon">
		<Name>Locked On</Name>
		<Desc>All enemies' Lightning Orbs deal damage to this character instead of dealing damage randomly. Only 1 character can be Locked On at a time. At the end of the Scene, lose Locked On.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

	<BattleEffectText ID="SlickMod_GamerCycle">
		<Name>Cycle</Name>
		<Desc>Upon using a page, discard 2 random pages, then draw 2 pages, then lose 1 Cycle.</Desc>
	</BattleEffectText>

  </effectTextList>
</BattleEffectTextRoot>