<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BookDescRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <bookDescList>

    <!--CANARD-->

    <!--URBAN MYTH-->

<!-- Sluggers -->
    <BookDesc BookID="2201001">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	‘The backstreet sluggers’ are us, an urban myth hazard syndicate composed of… about 8 people? We all were rats, scattered and stupid, and horribly weak, but after we met Ethan, he set us straight, trained us with exercises and sparring, and provided us a primary weapon: A wooden baseball bat, surprisingly reliable.

	Now we hunt those weaker than us, even if our boss wants us to “strike upward with our power” instead of down, preaching something, he still seemed annoyed with some of us, but it can't be helped, rats with bats, smashing the skulls of other rats, and the occasional fixer... Say, when was this paper in my pocket? Maybe I should show Ethan this...</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>

    <BookDesc BookID="2201002">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	All sorts of weapons within the city, from swords, to your own fists, to the fancy technology the Hana Association uses... but at the end of the day, all a weapon needs to do is to be able to take lives, or at least harm someone. In my case, it's this baseball bat. Made from wood, but pretty sturdy, and good enough at whacking fools and smashing skulls! Everyone has their preferences, but what if you didn't have to choose? A whole arsenal at your fingertips... Sounds like a dream.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>




    <!--URBAN LEGEND-->

    <!--URBAN PLAGUE-->

<!-- Midnight Office -->




    <!--URBAN NIGHTMARE-->

    <!-- Couriers -->
    <BookDesc BookID="2501001">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	I ain't gonna lie to you, slick. Workin' for the Thumb? Not all it's cracked up to be. Workin' directly under *any* Finger's not all that. Pinky's unhinged, Ring's a buncha stuck-up asshats, Middle can't take a damn joke, Index's a buncha wackos, 'n' the Thumb can't take a joke either. You ain't gonna find friends workin' for any of 'em. Yeah, yeah, City ain't no place to be chummy, but ya just can't help it; no man's an island. Not even D.C.. The camaraderie in the Thumb's all based on respect; not a damn thing else. So it ain't real camaraderie. Or, at least, it don't look real to me. Maybe that's just because I ain't some Soldato or Capo's drinkin' buddy, I dunno. Us Couriers, though? We may be special enough to be taken in by the Couriers in the first place, but the reality is... We ain't the best fighters. We ain't even in the top 50%. We ain't shit, and we know it. So we know we gotta stick together, have each others' backs, 'cuz nobody else will. I know that. The Extraordinaires know that. Even big man D.C. knows it.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>

    <!-- Snow Coyotes -->
    <BookDesc BookID="2502001">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	Life in District 25 ain't easy. Most of us joined up with the Snow Coyotes to avoid freezing to death out in the cold, or having the tax collectors find our bodies suspiciously dead. It's probably why Hansen thinks all of us are a bunch of good-for-nothing maggots. Though we're tougher than we look, thanks in part to the fact District 25 is cold all year round. Desperate people tend to make for desperate, lethal fighters. Least, that's what we like to tell ourselves. The whole saying of a cornered animal, and the like.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="2502002">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	You wanna know why the Snow Coyotes are a joke? Hansen smoked my ass 100 times in training. In a goddamn row. Not to mention the rank and file are a bunch of mostly starved, nearly frozen to death idiots who signed on just to avoid tax collectors. Not like Hansen's ever gonna take us seriously. Least there's Sera... Much as I hate the corpo exec and doing anything in her presence, she's funny when she's drunk, and doesn't know how to keep a lid on it. Childhood friends don't turn out to be good lifelong buddies, I guess. But I'm gonna make this shitshow work, if only to show Hansen that people from District 25 aren't a bunch of nobodies.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>

    <!-- Infernal Templars -->
    <BookDesc BookID="2503001">
      <BookName>An Inferno Corps Templar's Page</BookName>
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	---PROGRAM INITIATED | TRAINING FEEDBACK APPLIED---
Another day, another reason to hate this body. It has its uses, I suppose, but... These are supposed to be *our* bodies. Instead, we're... Just puppets. At any time, they can just flip a switch, and take the wheel, putting us in the back seat of our own bodies. It's horrifying... The only ones of us with any free will are the Seats, those who've wholly devoted themselves to... Whatever 'Their Grace' means... On second thought, I don't think I'd want to be one of them, either... Rumor has it one of them has been outed as a traitor. Who's to say there aren't more traitors? Who's to say they won't THINK there's more traitors?
Well, at least we’re heading to this Library place, by decree of Engineer Primus.
 It can't be that bad-
---COMBAT SYSTEMS ENGAGED | SUPPRESSING CONSCIOUSNESS---
</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="2503002">
      <BookName>An Inferno Corps Underunt's Page</BookName>
      <TextList>
        <Desc>	"Situation Report:
The Proxy was onto us. Found the weapon in progress; but didn’t act. Applied suggestion; Move weapon or raise fortifications..."

	Bah, who am I kidding... That fucker doesn't even care enough to show up. The Templars are soulless hunks of metal, and us “scouts” doing all their dirty work aren’t afforded any thought. Well, it could always be worse. The Seats could get involved... or the fucker himself.
</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <!--SUSSY IN THE CITY-->

    <!--WATSON TIER-->
+
    
  <!--PLACEHOLDERS-->
    <BookDesc BookID="10000006">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000007">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000008">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000009">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000010">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000011">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000012">
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
  </bookDescList>
</BookDescRoot>